let questions = [
    {
        numb: 0,
        question: "Ready to take the quiz again?",
        answer: "YES, I AM READY!",
        options: [
            "YES, I AM READY!",
            "NO",
            "yes",
            "no :("
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Who was the Danish physicist who accidentally discovered that a magnetic needle is deflected when the current in a nearby wire varies?",
        answer: "B) Hans Christian Oersted",
        options: [
            "A) André-Marie Ampere",
            "B) Hans Christian Oersted",
            "C) James Clerk Maxwell",
            "D) Joseph Henry" 
        ]
    },
{
    numb: 2,
    question: "Who formulated the famous law of electromagnetism that describes mathematically the magnetic force between two electrical currents?",
    answer: "B) André-Marie Ampere",
    options: [
        "A) Michael Faraday",
        "B) André-Marie Ampere",
        "C) Heinrich Hertz",
        "D) James Clerk Maxwell" 
    ]
},
{
    numb: 3,
    question: "What is the continuum of electromagnetic waves arranged according to frequency and wavelength?",
    answer: "A) electromagnetic spectrum",
    options: [
        "A) electromagnetic spectrum",
        "B) electromagnetism",
        "C) electron",
        "D) electricity" 
    ]
},
{
    numb: 4,
    question: "Among the EM waves, which one has photons with the lowest energy?",
    answer: "C) radio waves",
    options: [
        "A) gamma rays",
        "B) x-ray",
        "C) radio waves",
        "D) infrared" 
    ]
},
{
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which one among the EM waves has photons of high energies?",
    answer: "D) x-rays",
    options: [
        "A) microwaves",
        "B) ultraviolet",
        "C) visible light",
        "D) x-rays" 
    ]
},
{
    numb: 6,
    question: "What region of the electromagnetic spectrum are used in satellite communications?",
    answer: "D) microwaves",
    options: [
        "A) visible light waves",
        "B) radio waves",
        "C) x-rays",
        "D) microwaves" 
    ]
},
{
    numb: 7,
    question: "What law describes mathematically the magnetic force between two electrical currents?",
    answer: "B) Ampere's Law",
    options: [
        "A) Oersted's Law",
        "B) Ampere's Law",
        "C) Electromagnetic Law",
        "D) Faraday's Law" 
    ]
},
{
    numb: 8,
    question: "At what speed do electromagnetic waves travel in vacuum?",
    answer: "A) 3 x 10^8 m/s",
    options: [
        "A) 3 x 10^8 m/s",
        "B) 2 x 10^8 m/s",
        "C) 3 x 10 m/s",
        "D) 3 x 10^7 m/s" 
    ]
},
{
    numb: 9,
    question: "Who formulated the principle behind electromagnetic induction?",
    answer: "C) Michael Faraday",
    options: [
        "A) Hans Christian Oersted",
        "B) James Clerk Maxwell",
        "C) Michael Faraday",
        "D) Heinrich Rudolf Hertz" 
    ]
},
{
    numb: 10,
    question: "He showed experimental evidence of electromagnetic waves and their link to light.",
    answer: "A) Heinrich Hertz",
    options: [
        "A) Heinrich Rudolf Hertz",
        "B) Joseph Henry",
        "C) Andre-Marie Ampere",
        "D) Michael Faraday", 
    ]
},
{
    numb: 11,
    question: "He contributed to electromagnetism by developing equations that showed the relationship of electricity and magnetism.",
    answer: "D) James Clerk Maxwell",
    options: [
        "A) Michael Faraday",
        "B) Joseph Hnery",
        "C) Hans Christian Oersted",
        "D) James Clerk Maxwell" 
    ]
},
{
    numb: 12,
    question: "What do you call the bundles of wave energy?",
    answer: "B) photons",
    options: [
        "A) energy",
        "B) photons",
        "C) electromagnetic",
        "D) protons" 
    ]
},
{
    numb: 13,
    question: "What is our main source of ultraviolet light?",
    answer: "A) sun",
    options: [
        "A) sun",
        "B) energy",
        "C) light",
        "D) heat" 
    ]
},
{
    numb: 14,
    question: "What region of the electromagnetic spectrum is used in hospitals in producing images of internal tissues, bones, and organs?",
    answer: "B) x-ray",
    options: [
        "A) microwaves",
        "B) x-ray",
        "C) gamma rays",
        "D) visible light" 
    ]
},
{
    numb: 15,
    question: "As the wavelength increases, the frequency _______.",
    answer: "D) decreases",
    options: [
        "A) increases",
        "B) becomes zero",
        "C) remains the same",
        "D) decreases"
    ]
}
];
